So you may have to replace it with something close to it.
Now the first thing you're going to need to do when repairing one of these vinyl floor, flooring pieces is take your utility knife and you're actually going to want to cut off a corner of the tile.
So, you're going to want to do like that, and then if you can, in some cases you could actually get into the, that piece with the end of your razor blade and pick it out like this.
If you're lucky enough to be able to do that, then from there you can pretty much pick at it and tear that piece out.
If you can't get to it like that, you may have to get creative with a, like a chisel of some sort and just get a hammer and chisel it up, and then you can get a chisel from the other side and chisel that piece out.
Once you get that piece out, then you'll have to get whatever glue is on, on the floor, off, and how you can do that is you can use any kind of a cleaner to actually soak that area for a little while and you can scrape it up with a razor or you can sand that glue if that glue is really dry.
You can sand that glue smooth until you feel comfortable putting your other piece on, to make a smooth transition between the two pieces.
Once you get the glue off, you just simply, simply stick your other adhesive tile down in its place and you have a fixed adhesive tile.
Now there are other options if you're having trouble getting the adhesive tile off the floor, you can actually soak a rag in solvent and drape the rag over the top of the floor and cover it with plastic to keep the fumes from getting out and that will actually work on dissolving that glue underneath and may make it a little bit easier for you to get that piece out.
My name's Ryan Parker with Parker Home Renovations and you can contact me at: parkerhomerenovations.com.